Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection MSS.040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2008 - Series I: Documentary Material, 40139
  - Subseries B: People, 40140
    - Zemeckis, Robert: THE POLAR EXPRESS, 2004; 40142 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 116)
    - Zinnen, Al, n.d.; 40141 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 117)
- Accretions 2008 - Series II: Graphic Material, 40132
  Unless otherwise noted, Series II-A and II-B are in oversize boxes.
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork, 40135
    - Canemaker, John: THE FELT FAMILY, n.d.; 40138 (Box 2008.II.A.5, Folder 153)
    - Canemaker, John: Destination Modern Art: An Intergalactic Journey to MoMA and P.S.1, 2005 - 2006; 40137 (Box 2008.II.A.5, Folder 154)
    - Various: Presentation slides for "The Moving Image", 1991; 40136 (Box 2008.II.A.5, Folder 155)
  - Subseries B: Posters, 40133
    - Festivals & Screenings, 2005 - 2006; 40134 (Box 91, Folder 157)
- Accretions 2008 - Series III: Book Collection, 40131
  The book collection is housed in the Fales Library. The books have been catalogued in Bobcat. A keyword or related name search with the name Canemaker will retrieve the records for the books.
- Accretions 2008 - Series IV: Periodical Collection, 40127
  Unless noted below, the periodical collection have been catalogued in Bobcat. A keyword or related name search with the name Canemaker will retrieve the records for the periodicals.
  - Animation P.S.1 (MoMA), 2001 - 2002; 40130 (Box 91, Folder 156)
  - ASIFA, 2003; 40129 (Box 91, Folder 156)
  - ASIFA-EAST, 2004; 40128 (Box 91, Folder 156)
- Accretions 2008 - Series V: Audio & Video Tape Collection, 40076
  - Subseries B: Original Recordings, 40077
    - Recording for FINIAN'S RAINBOW: music & commentary by composer Yip Harburg, Part I, 1954; ID: 040.0101; 40126 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0101, Case 040.0101)
      Duration: 14 minutes
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell XLII 90
    - Recording for FINIAN'S RAINBOW: music & commentary by composer Yip Harburg, Part II, 1954; ID: 040.0102; 40125 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0102, Case 040.0102)
      Duration: 42 minutes
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell UDS-II 46
    - Irving Mendelsohn (friend of Winsor McCay) interview by Canemaker;| Canemaker at Cinemateque Screening of McCay films: FLYING HOUSE, PET & MOSQUITO PT. 1, August 12, 1974; ID: 040.0103; 40124 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0103, Case 040.0103)
      Duration: 60 minutes
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK D*C60
    - Midwest Film Fest, Frank Thomas & Ollie Johnston interview by Canemaker, Part I, 1981; ID: 040.0104; 40123 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0104, Case 040.0104 pt.1, Case 040.0104 pt.2)
      Duration: 89 minutes
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Instant Reply
    - Midwest Film Fest, Frank Thomas & Ollie Johnston interview by Canemaker, Part II, 1981; ID: 040.0105; 40122 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0105, Case 040.0105)
    - NPR Interview: Jim D'Anna & John Canemaker, May 7, 1986; ID: 040.0107; 40120 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0107, Case 040.0107)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Konica ML 90
    - Phone interview with Jean Adams (Daughter of Apthorp Adams, friend of Winsor McCay), recorded by Larry Ruppel and Greg Brown, c. 1986; ID: 040.0108; 40119 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0108, Case 040.0108)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK SA 60
    - Cannizzaro family watching home movies (later used in Canemaker's THE MOON AND THE SON"), July 3-5, 1982; ID: 040.0106; 40121 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0106, Case 040.0106)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Supertape Gold 90
    - Theo Halladay on her mother, Sylvia Maberly-Holland, Los Angeles, December 5, 1987; ID: 040.0109; 40118 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0109, Case 040.0109)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell UR 90
    - Phone interview with Hal Walker, FELIX THE CAT animator, July 4, 1989; ID: 040.0110; 40117 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0110, Case 040.0110 pt.1, Case 040.0110 pt.2)
      Duration: 85 minutes
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell XLII-S 90
    - Margaret J. Winkler Mintz & Bob and Katherine Fish (daughter of M.J. Winkler Mintz), December 2, 1989; ID: 040.0111; 40116 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0111, Case 040.0111)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK D60
    - Phone interview with George Winkler; | Phone interview with Joe D'Angelo (King Features Press), December 3, 1989 /December 21, 1989; ID: 040.0112; 40115 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0112, Case 040.0112)
      Duration: 56 minutes
    - John Canemaker speaks with Terry Guy on "Felix, the Twisted Tale of the World's Most Famous Cat," KPFK 90.7 FM, Los Angeles, 1990; ID: 040.0113; 40114 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0113, Case 040.0113)
      Duration: 40 minutes
      Access CD available.Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell XLII 90
    - Phone interview with Jerry and Fanny Babitsky Rabin (Art Babbitt's sister), March 22, 1992; ID: 040.0114; 40113 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0114, Case 040.0114)
      Duration: 48 minutes
    - Elsie Babbitt | Shamus Culhane, October 14, 1993/September 20, 1993; ID: 040.0115; 40112 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0115, Case 040.0115 pt.1, Case 040.0115 pt.2)
      Duration: 96 minutes
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK D90
    - Ray Favata on Bill Tytla & NYC animation for TV in 1950's, 60's, 70's, November 29, 1993; ID: 040.0116; 40111 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0116, Case 040.0116 pt.1, Case 040.0116 pt.2)
      Duration: 84 minutes
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK SA-X 90
    - Disney animators, 1993; ID: 040.0117; 40110 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0117, Case 040.0117 pt.1, Case 040.0117 pt.2)
      Duration: 95 minutes
      Access CD available.Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK D90
    - John Canemaker, FRESH AIR, 1993; ID: 040.0118; 40109 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0118, Case 040.0118)
      Original Format: Audiocassette
    - Kathy Rose | John Hench, December 28, 1993/January 6, 1994; ID: 040.0119; 40108 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0119, Case 040.0119 pt.1, Case 040.0119 pt.2)
    - Joe Grant | Marc Davis, January 7, 1994/January 10, 1994; ID: 040.0120; 40107 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0120, Case 040.0120 pt.1, Case 040.0120 pt.2)
    - Marc Davis, Fletridge, California | Frank Thomas & Ollie Johnston, Fletridge, California, January 10, 1994/ January 11, 1994; ID: 040.0121; 40106 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0121, Case 040.0121)
    - Kaleidoscope: Cardiff, Wales radio show hosted by Brian Sibley and featuring interviews with John Canemaker, Robin Allan, Joanna Quinn & Bob Godfrey, May 18, 1994; ID: 040.0122; 40105 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0122, Case 040.0122)
    - Faith Hubley interview by John Canemaker, Parts I & II, Bridgehampton, NY, June 21, 1996; ID: 040.0123; 40104 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0123, Case 040.0123 pt. 1, Case 040.0123 pt.2)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Sony 90
    - Faith Hubley interview, Parts III, July 20, 1996; ID: 040.0124; 40103 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0124, Case 040.0124)
    - Nick Park, NYU, New York City, October 21, 1996; ID: 040.0125; 40102 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0125, Case 040.0125)
    - Chuck Jones phone interview with John Canemaker on Tex Avery, c. 1996; ID: 040.0126; 40101 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0126, Case 040.0126 pt.1, Case 040.0126 pt.2)
    - Brenda Chapman, Steve Hickner & Simon Wells interview by John Canemaker on PRINCE OF EGYPT, August 12, 1998; ID: 040.0127; 40100 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0127, Case 040.0127)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Fuji DR-I 60
    - Peter Lord, Nick Park & Jeffrey Katzenberg on CHICKEN RUN, March 16, 2000; ID: 040.0128; 40099 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0128, Case 040.0128)
      Duration: 66 minutes.
    - Fred Schwartz on FINIAN'S RAINBOW, January 15, 2001; ID: 040.0129; 40098 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0129, Case 040.0129 pt.1, Case 040.0129 pt.2)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Fuji DR-I 90
    - Raman Hui, William Steig (creator of Shrek), Vicky Jenson & Andrew Adamson on SHREK, March 29, 2001; ID: 040.0130; 40097 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0130, Case 040.0130 pt.1, Case 040.0130 pt.2)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell UR 120
      Duration: 88 minutes.
    - Blue Sky interviews: Chuck Richardson, Mike Defeo (Lead Modeler) & John Donkin (Associate Producer) on ICE AGE, November 28, 2001; ID: 040.0131; 40096 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0131, Case 040.0131)
      Duration: 45 minutes.
    - Blue Sky interviews: Brian McEntee & Carlos Saldanha on ICE AGE, November 28, 2001; ID: 040.0132; 40095 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0132, Case 040.0132)
      Duration: 34 minutes.
    - Blue Sky interviews: Chris Wedge (Co-Director), Jerry David (Pre-Production), Dan Sheffelman (Story) & Moroni Taylor, November 28, 2001; ID: 040.0133; 40094 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0133, Case 040.0133 pt.1, Case 040.0133 pt.2)
    - Karal Ann Marling, January 14, 2002; ID: 040.0134; 40093 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0134, Case 040.0134)
      Duration: 25 minutes.
    - Pete Docter & Richard Williams from Pixar | Maggie Rich (Mary Blair's niece) on Mary Blair| Clark Spencer & Chris Sanders from Disney, March 15/17/19, 2002; ID: 040.0135; 40092 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0135, Case 040.0135 pt.1, Case 040.0135 pt.2)
      Duration: 109 minutes.
    - Rolly Crump | Frank Thomas | Kevin Blair | Neil Graner, April 23-24, 2002/April 30, 2002/May 1, 2002; ID: 040.0136; 40091 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0136, Case 040.0136 pt.1, Case 040.0136 pt.2)
      Duration: 124 minutes.
    - Alice Davis, Los Angeles, June 11, 2002; ID: 040.0137; 40090 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0137, Case 040.0137 pt.1, Case 040.0137 pt.2)
      Duration: 80 minutes.
    - Tissa David, September 18, 2002; ID: 040.0138; 40089 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0138, Case 040.0138 pt.1, Case 040.0138 pt.2)
    - Joe Grant, April 11, 2003; ID: 040.0139; 40088 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0139, Case 040.0139)
    - Andreas Hykade & Jacob Schuh (Studio 501), Ludwigsburg, Germany, November 28, 2003; ID: 040.0140; 40087 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0140, Case 040.0140_pt.1, Case 040.0140_pt.2)
      Duration: 86 minutes.
    - Pixar interviews: Ed Catmull (President of Pixar) interview by John Canemaker on THE INCREDIBLES, June 23, 2004; ID: 040.0141; 40086 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0141, Case 040.0141)
    - Pixar interviews: Mark Andrews (Story Supervisor), Steve Hunter, Alan Barillaro & Tony Fucile (Supervising Animators) & Katherine Sarafin (Production Manager) on THE INCREDIBLES, June 23, 2004; ID: 040.0142; 40085 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0142, Case 040.0142)
    - Pixar interviews: Brad Bird (Director) interview by John Canemaker on THE INCREDIBLES, June 24, 2004; ID: 040.0143; 40084 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0143, Case 040.0143)
      Duration: 36 minutes.
    - Pixar interviews: Rick Sayre (Supervising Technical Director) on THE INCREDIBLES, June 24, 2004; ID: 040.0144; 40083 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0144, Case 040.0144)
    - George E. & Deborah Miller (brother/sister-in-law of John Parr Miller), Part I, November 15, 2005; ID: 040.0145; 40082 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0145, Case 040.0145_pt.1, Case 040.0145_pt.2)
      Duration: 126 minutes.
    - George E. Miller, Part II | John Parr Miller, November 15, 2005/November 30, 2005; ID: 040.0146; 40081 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0146, Case 040.0146)
    - The Openended Group: Paul Kaiser, Shelley Eshkar & Marc Donnie, April 11, 2006; ID: 040.0147; 40080 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0147, Case 040.0147)
    - George Nicholson (literary agent) on Disney story artist J.P. Miller and Golden Books Publishing, May 31, 2006; ID: 040.0148; 40079 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0148, Case 040.0148)
      Duration: 56 minutes.
    - Margot MacDonald Bachman on J.D. Miller, Hampshire House, 150 CPS, New York City, December 5, 2006; ID: 040.0149; 40078 (Box 2008.V.7, Media ID: 040.0149, Case 040.0149_pt.1, Case 040.0149_pt.2)
- Accretions 2008 - Series VI: Major Projects, 40035
  - Subseries A: "The Art and Flair of Mary Blair", 40050
    - Book reviews, 2003; 40075 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 118)
    - Events: various related to book, n.d.; 40074 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 119)
    - Publicity, n.d.; 40073 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 120)
    - Blair, Mary, n.d.; 40072 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 121)
    - Blair, Donovan, 2002; 40071 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 122)
    - Blair, Kevin, 1994 - 2002; 40070 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 123)
    - Blair, Lee ***see also*** Blair, Mary, n.d.; 40069 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 124)
    - Blair, Preston ***see*** Blair, Lee, 1988; 40068
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to book, 40067 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 125)
    - Canemaker, John: Interviews: various related to research, 1994 - 2002; 40066 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 126)
    - Canemaker, John: Notes, n.d.; 40065 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 127)
    - Canemaker, John: Powerpoint lecture on Mary Blair, n.d.; 40064 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 128)
    - Canemaker, John: Research, n.d.; 40063 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 129)
    - Chamberlain, Jeanne, 1994 - 2002; 40062 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 130)
    - Crump, Roland, 1995 - 2002; 40061 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 131)
    - Davis, Marc & Alice, 1994 - 2002; 40060 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 132)
    - Disney, Walt: South American trip: General, 1941; 40059 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 133)
    - Disney, Walt: South American trip: AQUERELLA DO BRASIL, 1941 - 1942; 40058 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 134)
    - Disney, Walt: South American trip: SALUDOS AMIGOS, 1941 - 1995; 40057 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 135)
    - Grant, Joe, 1994 - 2003; 40056 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 136)
    - Grauer, Neil, 1994 - 2002; 40055 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 137)
    - Johnston, Ollie ***see*** Thomas, Frank, 1995; 40054
    - Richardson, Margaret @ Maggie Rich, 2002; 40053 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 138)
    - Robinson, Varda, n.d.; 40052 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 139)
    - Thomas, Frank, 1995 - 2002; 40051 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 140)
  - Subseries B: "The Animated Raggedy Ann & Andy", 40040
    - Bell, Carl, 1976; 40049 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 141)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to research, 1976; 40048 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 142)
    - Canemaker, John: Interviews: various related to research, 1976; 40047 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 143)
    - Canemaker, John: Interviews: various related to research, n.d.; 40046 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 144)
    - Canemaker, John: Notes on studio visits, 1976; 40045 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 145)
    - Gruelle, Worth, 1976 - 1977; 40044 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 146)
    - Williams, Dick, 1976; 40043 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 147)
    - The PEG-BOARD: Vol. 7, Nos. 2, 3, 5, 7 & 8, 1976; 40042 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 148)
    - Miscellaneous articles, n.d.; 40041 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 149)
  - Subseries C: "Walt Disney's Nine Old Men and the Art of Animation", 40036
    - Book reviews, 2001; 40039 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 150)
    - Correspondence: various related to book, 2001 - 2004; 40038 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 151)
    - Publicity: various related to book, n.d.; 40037 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 152)
- Accretions 2008 - Series VII: Objects, 40033
  - Disney, Walt: CHICKEN RUN, 2000; 40034 (Box 2008.VII.8)
- Accretions 2008 - Oversize - Series I: Documentary Material, 40026
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 40031
    - WAAW Studio: TEEN BII, n.d.; 40032 (Box I.A.5, Folder 158)
  - Subseries B: People, 40027
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA ***see also*** Series I-A, Box 1, Folder 4, 1990; 40030 (Box 83, Folder 159)
    - Disney, Walt: Walt Disney Family Museum, n.d.; 40029 (Box 83, Folder 160)
    - McCay, Winsor: Wonderland and Eden Musee, 40028 (Box 83, Folder 161)
- Accretions 2012 - Series I: Documentary Material, 242375
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 242376
    - The 1978 Los Angeles International Film Exposition, 242377 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 1)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [1 of 4], 2012; 242378 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 2)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [2 of 4], 2012; 242379 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 3)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [3 of 4], 2012; 242380 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 4)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [4 of 4], 2012; 242381 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 5)
    - Calendar - Jacob Burns Film Center, January/February 2004; 242382 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 6)
    - Celebrating the International Museum of Cartoon Art Collection, 2009; 242403 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 7)
    - Company - The Original Cast in Concert, April 1993; 242404 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 8)
    - Data/Interviews for Article on 2D vs. 3D Animation, 2002; 242405 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 9)
    - Drawings for Animated Films 1914-1978, c.1 and c.2, 242406 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 10)
    - Forbidden Animation, undated; 242407 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 11)
    - Ghetto Film School 2010 & 2011 - John Canemaker Guest Lectures, 2009-2011; 242408 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 12)
    - Imprint (Print Magazine) Online blog by John Canemaker, Mar. 4, 2010-Dec.13, 2010 http://imprint.printmag.com/john-canemaker/, 242474 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 13)
    - Irish Animation Research & Article by John Canemaker for Print Magazine Oct. 2010, 1989; 2008-2010; 242475 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 14)
    - The John Basmajian Collection of Walt Disney Animation Art - Christie's East, 1984; 242476 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 15)
    - Kinetica-2: A Centennial Tribute to Oskar Fischinger, 2000; 242477 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 16)
    - Lincoln Center's Walt Disney - 50th Anniversary Film Retrospective, 1973; 242478 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 17)
    - Mickey Mouse 1928-1978 The Bowers Museum, 242479 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 18)
    - The Moving Image, 1982; 242480 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 19)
    - "My Depression", 2005; 2009; 242481 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 20)
    - Nordisk Tidskrift on Animerad Film Story Board, 1989; 242482 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 21)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [1 of 5], 1979-1992; 242483 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 22)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [2 of 5], 1979-1992; 242484 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 23)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [3 of 5], 1979-1992; 242485 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 24)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [4 of 5], 1979-1992; 242486 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 25)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [5 of 5], 1979-1992; 242487 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 26)
    - OpenEnded Group, 1998-2009; 242488 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 27)
    - South Beach, FL Festival, 2009; 242489 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 28)
    - Visionfest 2005 Student Animation Competition, 242490 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 29)
    - Walt Disney Family Museum - opened S.F. 10/1/09, 2006-2009; 242491 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 30)
  - Subseries B: People, 242493
    - Bachert, Hildegard - A Memoir, 2010; 242494 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 31)
    - Canemaker, John - Article for D23 (Disney Magazine) Spring 2012, 2009-2012; 242495 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 32)
    - Canemaker, John - in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Aug. 28 (Mon.) - Sept. 3 (Sun.) 1995. 7th Banco Nacional Int'l Film Festival, 242496 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 33)
    - Canemaker, John - Introduction to 2012 Book of Mary Blair. Artwork for Golden Books., 2011; 242497 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 34)
    - Canemaker, John - NYU Distinguished Teaching Award, 2008-2009; 242498 (Box 2012.I.A.B.1, Folder 35)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [1 of 3], 2006-2012; 242499 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 1)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [2 of 3], 2006-2012; 242500 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 2)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [3 of 3], 2006-2012; 242501 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 3)
    - Canemaker, John - Teaching in Ireland Nov. 2009. Correspondence, Programs, Itinerary, Etc., 242502 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 4)
    - Natwick, Grim - The Art of Grim Natwick - Howard Lowery, 1991; 242503 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 5)
- Accretions 2012 - Series IV: Periodical Collection, 242504
  - 17th World Festival of Animated FIlm - Catalog, 2006; 242505 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 6)
  - 17th World Festival of Animated Film - Catalog: Films, 2006; 242506 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 7)
  - The 35th Annual Annie Awards, 2008; 242507 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 8)
  - Aiga: Journal of Graphic Design vol. 16 no. 1, 1998; 242508 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 9)
  - Animation Newsletter [Bob Karin] [1 of 3], 1984; 242509 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 10)
  - Animation Newsletter [Bob Karin] [2 of 3], 1984; 242510 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 11)
  - Animation Newsletter [Bob Karin] [3 of 3], 1984; 242511 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 12)
  - Animato! no. 21 (Spring 1991), no. 31 (Winter 1995), 1991; 1995; 242512 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 13)
  - Animator - no. 19 (Apr/Jun 1987), 242513 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 14)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 20 (Dec. 1973), no. 23 (Sept. 1974), no. 25 (Mar. 1975), 1973; 1974; 1975; 242514 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 15)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 33 (March 1977), no. 34 (June 1977), 242515 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 16)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 35 (Sept. 1977), no. 37 (Mar. 1978), 1977; 1978; 242516 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 17)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 39 (Sept. 1978), no. 41 (Mar. 1979), 1978; 1979; 242517 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 18)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 42 (June 1979), no. 43 (Sept. 1979), 242518 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 19)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 44 (Dec. 1979), no. 45 (March 1980), 1979; 1980; 242519 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 20)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 48 (Dec. 1980), no. 49 (March 1981), 1980; 1981; 242520 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 21)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 57 (March 1983), no. 63 (Sept. 1984), 1983; 1984; 242521 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 22)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 64 (Dec. 1984), no. 65 (March 1985), 1984; 1985; 242522 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 23)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 67 (Sept. 1985), no. 68 (Dec. 1985), 242523 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 24)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 70 (June 1986), no. 74 (June 1987), 1986; 1987; 242524 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 25)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 75 (Sept. 1987) (2 copies), 242525 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 26)
  - Christmas of '85 - Alexander Gallery, 1985; 242526 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 27)
  - Christmas of '86 - Alexander Gallery, 1986; 242527 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 28)
  - Collectors' Showcase - vol. 18 no. 5 (Sept./Oct. 1998), vol. 20 no. 1 (Jan./Feb. 2000), 1998; 2000; 242528 (Box 2012.I.IV.B.2, Folder 29)
  - The Comic Art Show - Whitney Museum of American Art - Summer 1983, 242529 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 1)
  - The Comics Journal - The Magazine of News and Criticism - no. 120 (March 1988), 242530 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 2)
  - Deep Focus - vol. 2 no. 2 (3 copies), 1989; 242531 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 3)
  - Disney Magazine (Fall 2001, Summer 2002), 2001; 2002; 242532 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 4)
  - Disney Magazine (Fall 2003) (2 copies), 242533 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 5)
  - Esopus (Fall 2011), 242534 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 6)
  - Fantioche - 1st International Animation Film Festival, Baden/Switzerland (Oct. 1995), 242535 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 7)
  - Fantioche - 2nd International Animation Film Festival, Baden/Switzerland (Sept. 1997), 242536 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 8)
  - Filmmakers Newsletter - vol. 7 no. 3 (Jan. 1974), vol 7 no. 6 (Apr. 1974), 242538 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 9)
  - Filmmakers Newsletter - vol. 7 no. 8 (June 1974), vol. 8 no. 3 (Jan. 1975), 1974; 1975; 242539 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 10)
  - Fine Animation Art & Related Items - Howard Lowery (2 copies), 1990; 242540 (Box 2012.IV.3, Folder 11)